<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Decidrr</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="input_hint">Type your yes or no question here.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_processing">ProcessingActivity</string>
    <string name="button_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_answer">The Answer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_initial">Decidrr</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Life in a fully developed first world country can be difficult when it comes to making those tough decisions. Throughout our everyday lives we encounter moments where simple judgment suddenly requires an extensive amount of attention and thought.  Do you stress over irrelevant choices?  Have you ever endlessly pondered a seemingly basic decision? Have you spent long hours contemplating the options available? Are you such a slave to technology that you need an advanced artificial intelligence to tell you how to live your life?  Well no more will these basic evaluation skills prevent us from making decisions! Introducing the “Advisorr”, a new advance in calculated assessment software that is sure to change your life forever!  Our innovative team of professional engineers, software developers, and PHD psychologists have come together to create something truly extraordinary. By combining the latest advances in psychoanalytical technology, it has never been easier to make decisions with the simple touch of a button. By typing in a yes or no question, you are instantly connected to our vast information database, which processes and analyses the unique linguistic properties of your question. By calculating this information along with our vast historical decision resources, thousands of computer generated simulations are run simultaneously, in order to identify the outcome which bears the most productive result. All of this computation is done in a matter of seconds, and our knowledge perception engine immediately generates a fully functional, scientific community supported, NASA Endorsed, “Yes” or “No” response that best fits the individual supporter.  In addition “Advisorr” is programed to become familiar and accustomed to each user as an individual. As you continue to use the application in your daily life, our state-of-the-art recollection apparatus will begin to acclimatize your unique lexicon, and questioning process, to further develop responses that will best fit you as an individual.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tweets">Tweets</string>

</resources>
